dir2dir.net 2011-11-02

# Dir2Dir.Net Directory - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy The privacy of our clients is of utmost importance to Directory Services.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or if you wish to update information we hold about you or you wish to make a related complaint or to receive a copy of our current Privacy Policy Statement, please contact webmaster. 

**Types of Personal Information we collect** ** **

The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us.

For the directory service order, we would generally require your name, address, telephone number etc., which would be stored in your individual profile. In some instances we will also require your credit card details and other information.

 **  
Why we collect personal information** ** **

Generally we collect, update and use personal information about you to allow us to transact business on your behalf.

We may choose to add your details to our database for the purpose of directing opportunities to your attention. At any time, if you do not wish to continue receiving this information, you can inform us by the email and your details will be removed.

 **How we collect personal information**

Generally, we collect personal information directly from you. We may collect and update that information over the Internet by correspondence.

 **How we store information**

We store personal information in a combination of secure computer storage facilities. We have taken a number of steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse, loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

We also take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when we no longer need it.

 **  
When we may disclose your personal information**

Because your privacy is important we will not disclose your personal information without your consent.

However we may disclose personal information about you in the following circumstances:

* Where our business partners need to provide you with information and offers about products and services.

 **Access to personal information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If your personal details change, please contact us so that we can continue to provide you with our products and services.

We undertake to promptly acknowledge and investigate any complaints about the way we manage personal information.

 **About this Privacy Policy Statement**

We may update our policies and this Privacy Policy Statement from time to time.

 **  
Contact us**

If you have any questions about this policy, or wish to update information we hold about you, make a related complaint, or to receive a copy of our current Privacy Policy Statement, please contact webmaster.
